RG 071, Department of Housing
Connecticut State Library
Department of Housing records
1943-1994
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. Dept. of Housing
148.5 cubic feet
The Department of Housing handled all matters relating to housing and community development, including policy, development, redevelopment, preservation, maintenance and improvement of housing and neighborhoods.
RG071
Multiple
Historical Note
The State Housing Authority was established in 1943. On January 3, 1951 its duties and responsibilities transferred to the Department of Public Works, Housing Division. They transferred again in 1967 to the Department of Community Affairs, Bureau of Housing. The Department of Community Affairs was abolished in 1977 and its housing programs were consolidated under the Department of Economic Development. On July 1, 1977 the Department of Housing was established. Responsibilities for operating established state housing programs were transferred from the Department of Economic Development and the Department of Housing became the lead agency for housing matters. On October 1, 1995 the Department of Housing merged into the new Department of Economic and Community Development, becoming the Housing Division.
See also the.
Arrangement
Series 1. Commissioner, 1979-1994, 25 cubic feet.
Subject Files
Joseph E. Canale, 1979-1986, Accession: 1989-008, 11 cubic feet
John F. Papandrea, 1986-1990, 6 cubic feet
Accession: 1991-020, 1986-1990, 5 cubic feet
Accession: 1992-011, 1987-1989, 1 cubic foot
Henry S. Scherer, 1990-1994, Accession: 1995-032, 6 cubic feet
Executive Assistant Bob Hardiman: Accession: 1989-008, 2 cubic feet
Series 2. Deputy Commissioner, 1981-1988, 38 cubic feet.
Subject Files
David W. Deakin, 1978-1988, Accession: 1989-008, 21 cubic feet.
Victor Cruse, 1981-1986, 12 cubic feet
Accession: T003128, 11 cubic feet
Accession: 1991-020, 1 cubic foot
Yasha M. Escalera, 1987-1988, Accession: 1991-020, 5 cubic feet
Series 3. Department of Community Affairs, 1943-1980, 32.5 cubic feet.
Block Grants, 1945-1978, 22.5 cubic feet
Accession: 1985-026A, 1950-1966, 11 cubic feet
Accession: 1986-010B, 1945-1975, 4 cubic feet
Accession: 1989-005, 1958-1978, 2.5 cubic feet
Accession: 2004-025, 1959-1977, 5 cubic feet
Pilot Programs, 1968-1972, Accession: 1989-003, 2 cubic feet
Planning Maps, circa 1943-1980, Accession: T003133, 8 cubic feet
Series 4. Office of Legal Assistance and Relocation, 1962-1984, 50 cubic feet.
Appeals Files, 1962-1984, Accession: 1991-006, 50 cubic feet
Series 5. Innovative Housing and Special Initiative Division, 1983-1989, 1 cubic foot.
Director's Subject Files (T. Fusaro), 1983-1989, Accession: 1991-027, 1 cubic foot
Series 6. Policy and Planning Division, 1984, 1 cubic foot.
Correspondence and face sheets, 1984, Accession: 1992-022, 1 cubic foot
Series 7. Management Analysts, undated, 1 cubic foot.
Policy and Procedures Manual, undated, Accession: 1990-006, 1 cubic foot
Related Material
RG005 Office of the Governor records
Other Finding Aid
See also
Inventory of Department of Housing Planning Maps
.
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. Dept. of Community Affairs; Connecticut. Dept. of Housing
Persons:
Canale, Joseph E.; Cruse, Victor; Deakin, David W.; Escalera, Yasha M.; Papandrea, John F.; Scherer, Henry S.
Subjects:
Connecticut. Dept. of Housing -- Records and correspondence; Connecticut. Dept. of Community Affairs -- Records and correspondence; Connecticut Housing Authority -- Records and correspondence; Connecticut. Public Works Dept -- Records and correspondence; Housing -- Connecticut; Community development -- Connecticut
Document Types:
Contracts; Correspondence; Employees' manuals; Maps; Reports
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Series 1. Commissioner, 1979-1994; 25 cubic feet
  - Subject Files
    - Joseph E. Canale, 1979-1986; 1989-008; 11 cubic feet
      - ABCD Housing Advisory Committee (Box 1)
      - Accounting Manual (Box 1)
      - Activity reports (Box 1)
      - Administration, Bureau of (Box 1)
      - Administration Division, Pond, 1983-1987; 2 folders (Box 1)
      - Administrative memos (Box 1)
      - Administrative procedures (Box 1)
      - Aministrative Services, Department of (Box 1)
      - Affirmative action, Ken Warren (Box 1)
      - Affirmative action, 2 folders (Box 1)
      - Affirmative action meetings (Box 1)
      - Affirmattive Fair Housing (Box 1)
      - Affordable Housing Program, 1986 (Box 1)
      - Agency Achievements, DOH, Summary (Box 1)
      - Aging, Department on (Box 1)
      - AHEPA #58, Inc. (Box 1)
      - Appropriations, Budget (Box 1)
      - Attendance records (Box 1)
      - Attendance records, Comp time (Box 1)
      - Commissioner's Office attendance, 1987 March 13 - 26 (Box 1)
      - Attendance records, 1987 February 12 (Box 1)
      - Attendance records, 1987 March 12 - 1987 April 9 (Box 1)
      - Attendance sheets, 1981-1987; 7 folders (Box 1)
      - Connecticut Housing Finance authority (CHFA) (Box 2)
      - CHFA (Box 2)
        - Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 2)
        - Operating plan, 1985 (Box 2)
        - Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 2)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 2)
        - Single Family Construction Pilot Program, Mortgage Committee, 1985 February 22 (Box 2)
        - Miscellaneous, 1983-1984 (Box 2)
        - News releases (Box 2)
        - Proposed regulations (Box 2)
        - Savings and Loan League of CT vs. CT. Hsg. Finance Authority (Box 2)
        - Employee handbook (Box 2)
        - Conn. Housing Finance Authority and Annual operating plan, 1982 (Box 2)
        - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1979-1982; 4 folders (Box 2)
      - Connecticut Law Journal (Box 2)
      - Aging, Committee on, News (Box 2)
      - HUD, Bulletins (Box 2)
      - Law Enforcement Assistance Agency (LEAA) (Box 2)
      - Management update (Box 2)
      - Miscellaneous bulletins, newsletters, Ect. (Box 2)
      - Community Development Block Grant (Box 2)
      - National Governors' Association, Bulletins (Box 2)
      - NAHRO Monitor (Box 2)
      - NAHRO News alert (Box 2)
      - National Asso. Of Regional Councils (NARC) (Box 2)
      - Public Management (Box 2)
      - Attendance records, 1979-1980; 2 folders (Box 3)
      - Attorney General, New Haven Uniform relocation assistance (Box 3)
      - Attorney General" s Office, 1985-1986 (Box 3)
      - Attorney General's Office (Box 3)
        - Opinions and miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 3)
        - Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 3)
        - Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 3)
        - Opinions and miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 3)
        - Opinions and miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 3)
        - Opinions, 1980 (Box 3)
      - Audit, Miscellaneous (Box 3)
      - Auditors of Public Accounts, 2 folders (Box 3)
      - Audit, State, 1981 December 23 (Box 3)
      - Auditors' report, 1983 (Box 3)
      - Benjamin, James, Supv. Planning Sec. (Box 3)
      - Better Hartford enterprise (Box 3)
      - Bills, Letters in response to (Box 3)
      - Biloon, Sandra, Personnel (Box 3)
      - Bomb threats (Box 3)
      - Bridgeport, Greater R.H.C. (Box 3)
      - Budget, DOH (Box 3)
      - Building Code, State of Connecticut (Box 3)
      - Building Maintenance Survey, 1179 Main Street, Hartford, 1986 (Box 3)
      - Building Saftey, 1179 Main Street, Hartford (Box 3)
      - CAFCA (Box 3)
      - CCDA, Small cities (Box 3)
      - Capitol Housing Corporation (Box 3)
      - Capitol Region Conference of Churches (Box 3)
      - Catholic Charities, Board of Directors (Box 3)
      - Connecticut Community Development Asso. (Box 3)
      - Central Housing Committee (Box 3)
      - Central Housing Committee Task Force (Box 3)
      - Checking accounts (Box 3)
      - CHFA/DOH, Statutory Analyses (Box 3)
      - Connecticut Housing Investment Fund (Box 3)
      - Children, Commission on (Box 3)
      - Christmas party (Box 3)
      - Chronological, Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 3)
      - Citibank, NYC (Box 3)
      - Citizens' Advisory Council (Box 3)
      - Codes and Standards, Bureau (Box 3)
      - COE, Robert J., C and M Section (Box 3)
      - Colonial reality Co. (Box 3)
      - Community Development Block Grant (Box 3)
      - Comptroller, State of Ct., Miscellaneous (Box 3)
      - Condominium Conversion (Box 3)
      - Condominium conversion regulations (Box 3)
      - Condominium purchase, P.A. 80-396 (Box 3)
      - Coalition of Northeastern Governors, 1980 January 16 (Box 3)
      - Congregate Housing (Box 3)
      - Congregate Housing Committee (Box 3)
      - Congressional Record Reports (Box 3)
      - Conklin, James P., Mortgage service (Box 3)
      - Connecticut Association of Realtors, Inc. (Box 3)
      - Connecticut Bank and Trust Co. (Box 3)
      - Conservation and development polices plan (Box 3)
      - Construction activity report (Box 3)
      - Construction and maintance MR and elderly projects (Box 3)
      - Consumer Cooperatives, Task Force (Box 3)
      - Contracts, Miscellaneous Info. (Box 3)
      - Convent of Mercy (Box 3)
      - Corporation for Independent Living (Box 3)
      - Council of State Community Agencies (Box 3)
      - Connecticut Public Television (Box 3)
      - Capitol Region Council of Governments (Box 3)
      - Cruse, Victor R., Deputy Commissioner (Box 3)
      - Daniel, Lora Ann (Box 4)
      - Data Sheet, D.O.H. (Box 4)
      - Data Processing, Long Range (Box 4)
      - Deakin, David M. (Box 4)
      - Dedications and Groundbreakings (Box 4)
      - Demolition program (Box 4)
      - Development Division, Fusaro (Box 4)
      - Disaster, Civil Preparedness (Box 4)
      - Disaster planning for elderly Housing Projects (Box 4)
      - Donen, Steven, Legislative and Regulations (Box 4)
      - Down payment assistance program, Second mortgage, 1982 (Box 4)
      - Down payment assistance program, 1982 (Box 4)
        - Second mortgage, 1982 (Box 4)
      - Duffy, Michael T. (Box 4)
      - Duffy, Michael T. (Box 4)
        - Managers' Meetings Minutes (Box 4)
        - Performance appraisal (Box 4)
      - Dunnells, Duval, Benett and Porter (Box 4)
      - Economic Development, Department of (Box 4)
      - Elderly Housing Projects assignments (Box 4)
      - Elderly Housing (Box 4)
        - Project numbers (Box 4)
        - regulations income limits (Box 4)
      - Electrically-Heated Elderly and Congregate Housing (Box 4)
      - Emergency fuel assistance (Box 4)
      - Emergency Housing Fund (Box 4)
      - Emergency Operations (Box 4)
      - Emergency Personnel (Box 4)
      - Emergency Powers of Commissioner DOH (Box 4)
      - Emergency Shelter (Box 4)
      - Emergency Powers, Civil Preparedness, Windsor, Windsor Locks (Box 4)
      - Employee Listing D.O.H (Box 4)
      - Energy Advisory Board, Connecticut (Box 4)
      - Energy, Federal (Box 4)
      - Energy Conservation and solar Bank (Box 4)
      - Energy conservation Loan program, 1983; 2 folders (Box 4)
      - Energy programs, State (Box 4)
      - Energy and Public Utilities, Hearing (Box 4)
      - Environmental classification, Proposed, Stephen Heintz (Box 4)
      - Escalera, Yasha, Deputy Commissioner (Box 4)
      - Environmental Policy Act (Box 4)
      - Ethics Commission, Conn. State (Box 4)
      - Executive orders, Governor (Box 4)
      - Fair Housing Association of Conn. (Box 4)
      - Fair Rent Commissions (Box 4)
      - Federal Fund Report (Box 4)
      - Federal National Mortgage Association (Box 4)
      - Federal Grant Programs, Info. (Box 4)
      - Federal Register (Box 4)
      - Federal Emergency Management Agency, 2 folders (Box 4)
      - Finance Advisory Committee (Box 4)
      - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 4)
      - Fire safety (Box 4)
      - Fiscal Analysis, Office of (Box 4)
      - Five-Year Plan advisory committee (Box 4)
      - Fleet Operations, S. Negri, 1980-1985; 2 folders (Box 4)
      - Flex time (Box 4)
      - Flood Disaster, 1982, 1984; 2 folders (Box 4)
      - Four-day work week (Box 4)
      - Freedman, Elisha C., DAS (Box 4)
      - Freedom of Information (Box 4)
      - Funding requests, Federal (Box 4)
      - Furniture storage list (Box 4)
      - Fusaro, Ted, Supervisor (Box 4)
      - Futures Task Force (Box 4)
      - General Fund Status Reports (Box 4)
      - General letters, DAS (Box 4)
      - General Letters, L.H.A.'s and Municipalities (Box 4)
      - Gians, Humbert, audit (Box 4)
      - Governor William O"Neill (Box 4)
        - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 4)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 4)
        - Report on DOH activities during this administration (Box 4)
        - Bi-weekly reports (Box 4)
        - Voluntary action (Box 4)
        - Executive orders (Box 4)
        - Report on anticipated activities (Box 4)
        - Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 4)
        - Wahington Office (Box 4)
      - Grand Lists and percentage of tax rates (Box 4)
      - Grasso, Governor, Eulogy (Box 4)
      - Handicapped, Definition (Box 5)
      - Handi-tap, Convention (Box 5)
      - Hardiman, Robert M., Spec. Assistant (Box 5)
      - Hawkins, Lee, Governor's Office (Box 5)
      - Health, Department of (Box 5)
      - Health Insurance Information (Box 5)
      - Health Problems, DOH (Box 5)
      - Health systems agency, South West Connecticut (Box 5)
      - Hesse, Joseph, Business Office (Box 5)
      - Health, Education and Welfare (Box 5)
      - Hiring process, 1981 June 6 (Box 5)
      - Historical Commission, Connecticut (Box 5)
      - Hispanics, Housing programs used by hispanics (Box 5)
      - Holiday Inn, Brochure (Box 5)
      - Home Builders Association of Connecticut (Box 5)
      - Home equity conversion plans for the elderly, task force (Box 5)
      - Homeless, Innovative Housing (Box 5)
      - Housing, Complete list of State financed congregate,M.R. and elderly (Box 5)
      - Housing and land use (Box 5)
      - Housing, Department of (Box 5)
        - Conference, 1983 (Box 5)
        - Lease (Box 5)
        - Summary (Box 5)
      - Housing Coordinating Council (Box 5)
      - Housing Court (Box 5)
      - Housing Court, Citizens' Advisory Council (Box 5)
      - Housing, Department of, Data (Box 5)
      - Housing Department task force (Box 5)
      - Housing site development (Box 5)
      - Housing purchase and rehab fund, 2 folders (Box 5)
      - Housing Starts, Activity reports (Box 5)
      - Housing and urban development (Box 5)
        - Miscellaneous, 1979-1986; 5 folders (Box 5)
        - Reduced level of add"l subsidized housing (reagan), 1981 (Box 5)
        - John McLean (Box 5)
        - Section 8 (Box 5)
        - Sale of project notes (Box 5)
        - Testimony re moving of Hartford area office (Box 5)
      - Hudson, Fleeta (Box 5)
      - Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 5)
      - Human Services Commission (Box 5)
      - Human services agenda process (Box 5)
      - Income Maintenance, S. Heintz (Box 5)
      - Infill Housing program (Box 5)
      - Infoline of North central Connecticut (Box 5)
      - Ingersoll, Aldon T. (Box 5)
        - Administration (Box 5)
        - Grievance (Box 5)
        - Miscellaneous Memos (Box 5)
      - Inspector General, Miscellaneous (Box 5)
      - Insulation in State-Financed Housing (Box 5)
      - Insurance Forms (Box 5)
      - Insurance, Miscellaneous (Box 5)
      - Insurance Purchasing Board, State of Connecticut (Box 5)
      - Internal Audit, Henderson (Box 5)
      - Internal Audit, Vasile (Box 5)
      - Inventory, DOH Files, records, ect. (Box 5)
      - Kensington square development corp. New haven, CT (Box 5)
      - Kodak, copier, miscellaneous material (Box 5)
      - CHFA Meeting, 1987 January 29 (Box 6)
      - CHFA Meeting, 1987 February 26 (Box 6)
      - Department of Housing, folder (Box 6)
      - Untitled folder, 3 inches (Box 6)
      - CHFA, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 6)
      - Bloomfield, Town of (Box 6)
      - Bridgeport Housing Authority (Box 6)
      - Bridgeport, Beardsley and Pequonnock (Box 6)
      - Bridgeport projects, Beardsley and Pequonnock, 1980 (Box 6)
      - Bridgeport projects, Beardsley Terr. and Pequonnock Apts. (Box 6)
      - Bridgeport, HSD agency (Box 6)
      - Bristol Housing Authority (Box 6)
      - Brookfield Housing Authority (Box 6)
      - Brooklyn Housing Authority (Box 6)
      - Brooklyn Section 8 Office (Box 6)
      - Canton Housing Authority (Box 6)
      - CHA Staff meetings, commissioner's copy (Box 7)
      - Connecticut Housing Authority (Box 7)
      - East Hampton housing Authority (Box 7)
      - Unsorted material, 9 inches (Box 7)
      - Updike, Kelly and Spellacy, P.C. (Box 7)
      - Regulations, DOH, 1984 (Box 8)
      - Ragno, Louis, contract re MR manual (Box 8)
      - Public Housing revolving fund (Box 8)
      - Public Housing Managers, Connecticut Housing Authority (Box 8)
      - Public Housing Corporationof Hartford (Box 8)
      - Public hearings, OPM (Box 8)
      - Protest meeting, re: Governor's luncheon, CHC, 1979 September (Box 8)
      - Processing Assistance agreements, procedure (Box 8)
      - Progress reports, DOH (Box 8)
      - Shiver, Jack, Virginia Ventures (Box 8)
      - Press Releases, Governor O"Neill (Box 8)
      - Press releases outgoing, SBC (Box 8)
      - Press releases, Bond Commission (Box 8)
      - Bond Commission meeting (Box 8)
      - Press releases, Bond Commission, 1986 (Box 8)
      - Bond Commission meeting schedule, 1982, 1983, 1984, 1985, 1986 (Box 8)
      - Bond Fund, Housing, Statutory citations (Box 8)
      - Bond funds, unallocated (Box 8)
      - Bond fund reports, 1984 (Box 8)
      - Bond fund status report, 1982-1983 (Box 8)
      - Bond authorizations, DOH (Box 8)
      - SBC Press releases (Box 8)
      - Bond Commission, Misc. info (Box 8)
      - Banking Department, State of Connecticut (Box 8)
      - Bond commission meeting (Box 8)
      - Bond Commission meetings, 1986 (Box 8)
      - Labor rates, residential (Box 9)
      - La Casa De Puerto Rico, Inc. (Box 9)
      - Land use reports (Box 9)
      - Lamb, John W., Deputy Director (Box 9)
      - LandLord tenant information (Box 9)
      - Landmark development, Leon Brock (Box 9)
      - Law Revision Commission (Box 9)
      - Legal opinion on Housing Authority powers of the Commissioner of Housing (Box 9)
      - Legislation, 1980-1985; 4 folders (Box 9)
      - Legal Assistance and relocation appeals (Box 9)
      - Legislative Black Caucus (Box 9)
      - Legislative program review and investigative committee (Box 9)
      - Liebson, Alice R. (Box 9)
      - Life cycle cost analysis (Box 9)
      - Long Term Care Commission (Box 9)
      - Lopez, Marcia (Box 9)
      - Mail service, Info (Box 9)
      - Mail service and duplicating operations coordinators (Box 9)
      - Mail service and Hartford zip codes (Box 9)
      - Mailing lists (Box 9)
      - Management Advisory council (Box 9)
      - Management division, Duffy (Box 9)
      - Management incentive plan (Box 9)
      - Management Information, 1986-1987; 2 folders (Box 9)
      - Managers and commissioners, meetings (Box 9)
      - Management information (Box 9)
      - Management Task Force (Box 9)
      - Manual Updating, Housing (Box 9)
      - Manufactured Housing (Box 9)
      - March Inc., Manchester (Box 9)
      - Market report, Connecticut Housing (Box 10)
      - Mental health, Department of (Box 10)
      - Mental Retardation, Department of (Box 10)
      - Miano, Charles J. (Box 10)
      - Milano, Anthony, OPM, 1980-1986; 3 folders (Box 10)
      - Mileage Reports, Commissioner, Monthly, 1979-1987; 2 folders (Box 10)
      - Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 10)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 10)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 10)
        - Federal, Senators and representatives (Box 10)
        - State, Senators and representatives (Box 10)
      - Mobile and manufactured home advisory council (Box 10)
      - Mobile homes (Box 10)
      - Mobile Homes Task Force (Box 10)
      - Moderate Rental Housing Loan Program, Legal manual (Box 10)
      - Moderate Rental regulations (Box 10)
      - Moderate Rental Loan program (Box 10)
      - Moderate rental program (Box 10)
      - Modular and mobile elderly homes (Box 10)
      - Monitoring procedures, for DOH, support programs (Box 10)
      - Mortgage finance unit (Box 10)
      - Multi-family Housing (Box 10)
      - Multi-Unit Housing for Older adults statewide inventory (Box 10)
      - McCollam, Charles, Executive aide (Box 10)
      - NAHRO (Box 10)
        - Twenty-Ninth Annual Conference (Box 10)
        - Connecticut (Box 10)
        - Untitled folder (Box 10)
        - Futures Task Force (Box 10)
      - National Governor's Association (Box 10)
      - Navy, U.S. Department of (Box 10)
      - Negri, Stephen, Director of Fleet Operations, 1982 (Box 10)
      - Neighborhood Housing Services (Box 10)
      - Neighborhoood Preservation and Urban act (Box 10)
      - Neighborhood rehabilitation (Box 10)
      - Neighborhood reinvestment corporation (Box 10)
      - Nemiroff, P.I., corporation (Box 10)
      - New York State (Box 10)
      - News releases, DOH (Box 10)
      - Newspaper Articles (Box 11)
      - Officials, mailing list (Box 11)
      - Official designees to boards, agencies, committees, Ect. (Box 11)
      - Oickle, George (Box 11)
      - One-stop applications for development (Box 11)
      - Office of Policy and Management, 1982-1987; 3 folders (Box 11)
      - Office of Policy and Management, Budget (Box 11)
      - Organizational Info (Box 11)
      - OSHA, Labor relations (Box 11)
      - Parking, spaces, vandalism, ect. (Box 11)
      - Pension Fund, State employee's investment mortgage info (Box 11)
      - Personnel, Early closings and late openings info (Box 11)
      - Pet bill, P.A. 83-43 (Box 11)
      - Pilot, Misc. Info (Box 11)
      - Plan Review section, misc. info (Box 11)
      - Planning and development committee, general assembly (Box 11)
      - Planning and legislation unit (Box 11)
      - Planning and policy (Box 11)
      - policies, Investment and interest (Box 11)
      - Population statistics (Box 11)
      - Positions funding (Box 11)
      - Powers of the Commissioner of Housing, Legal opinion (Box 11)
    - John F. Papandrea, 1986-1990; 6 cubic feet
      - 1991-020, 5 cubic feet
        - Emergency Certification (Box 1)
        - DAS, Personnel division organization chart (Box 1)
        - Affirmative Action (Box 1)
        - Affordable Housing (Box 1)
        - Attorney General (Box 1)
        - Audits (Box 1)
        - Bond Commission meetings (Box 1)
        - Bonding, Legislation, 1987 (Box 1)
        - Bond Commission deadlines (Box 1)
        - Budget options (Box 1)
        - Clemente Roberto (Box 1)
        - Colchester (Box 1)
        - Community Renewal Team (Box 1)
        - Connecticut Association for Human Services (Box 1)
        - Conn. Assoc. of Realtors (Box 1)
        - CT. Conference on Municipalities (Box 1)
        - Conn. Assoc. for Community Action (Box 1)
        - Conn. Housing Authority (Box 1)
        - COSCA (Box 1)
        - The Council of Concern of Meriden (Box 1)
        - Capitol Region Council of Government (Box 1)
        - Lincoln Davis (Box 1)
        - Democratic State Central Committee (Box 1)
        - Elderhouse (Box 1)
        - El Hogar (Box 1)
        - Development Correspondence (Box 1)
        - Planning and Development Testimony, Ect. (Box 1)
        - Director's meetings (Box 1)
        - Economic Development (Box 1)
        - Fairfield County Day (Box 1)
        - Forever Housing Committee, 1987 (Box 1)
        - Governor's Correspondence (Box 2)
        - Governor's monthly report (Box 2)
        - Finance Revenue Bonding (Box 2)
        - Flex time, 1987 (Box 2)
        - Freedom of Information Commission (Box 2)